Gayan Charith Elgiriya Witharana

+60 1135532399 +94 712506380 Kenwingston Square Garden, Persiaran Bestari, 63000, cyberjaya, Selangor, Malaysia. vgayancharith@gmail.com https://github.com/gayancharith www.linkedin.com/in/gayanwitharan

PROFILE

Experienced Senior Software Engineer with a Bachelor of Computer Science, currently working at a well reputed company in Sri Lanka who has more than 5 years of working history in the computer software industry. I am a person with a passion for developing innovative systems that accelerates the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success.

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

- JavaScript, ES6+
- React, React-native, Redux
- PHP, Lumen, Silex, Eloquent
- Node js, Sails js
- GraphQl
- Circleci CI/CD

- Mysql, Couchbase, Mongodb
- .Net Core 2
- HTML and CSS
- Jquery, Vue js
- GitHub, GitLab, Trello and Atlassian Jira

EXPERIENCES

Archisoft Global Sdn Bhd. (Pvt) Ltd (Feb 2020 - Present)

Senior Front-End Developer

Esshva techq(Pvt) Ltd (Feb 2019 - Jan 2020)

Senior Software Engineer

Thinkcube Systems (Pvt) Ltd (Jan 2017 - Feb 2019)

Senior Software Engineer

Thinkcube Systems (Pvt) Ltd

(Jan 2014 - Jan 2017) Software Engineer Thinkcube Systems (Pvt) Ltd

(Jul 2013 - Jan 2014)

Trainee Software Engineer

PROJECTS

MTX

reactjs, netxtjs, redux, react-hooks

A Business to Business application with an admin panel.

Xforce (https://xforce.cornerstonex.com.my/)

reactjs, nextjs, redux, react-hooks

An employee management web application with an admin panel.

Madthread - Singapore

Reactjs, Node js, GraphQl, Mongodb, React-native, react hooks, redux, redux-thunk

A subscription base web system and mobile application to facilitate renting and buying clothes.

Webestory

Reactjs, react hooks, redux, redux-thunk, draft.js, react ant design

Webestory is an online diary that users can write memories with recordings, videos and share a specific part of the memory with specific friends.

Automobile classifieds and cashoffer system - USA

reactjs, redux, redux-thunk, redux-persist, reactive-search, .net core 2 - 2.2 serenity, microservices architecture, rest web-api, react hooks, redux selectors, jest

Classifieds facilitate users to showcase automobiles and receive cashoffer. This also includes inventory and co-part management as well as additional services such as transportation and safe-exchange.

eGN Web App

Php, lumen, Vue js, ecmascript-6, couchbase, webpack

Web application that manages citizens data for Sri Lanka government. The application is based on micro service architecture.

Agrinous	Mobile	App	(www.agrinous.com)	

reactjs, react-native, redux, redux-saga, wix-react-native-navigation, ecmascript-6, redux selectors, jest, e2e testing, appium, couchbase-lite

Mobile application for real time processing of livestock sales in Australia. This application handles eid scanning with bluetooth technology to handle stock management, selling and delivery sections.

Agrinous Web App (www.agrinous.com)

Php, silex, reactjs, redux, redux-saga, ecmascript-6, couchbase

Web application that manages livestock sales in Australia same as the mobile application.

Hudlmo Web Portal (www.hudlmo.com)

Node js, Sails js, mongodb, mocha, grunt, javascript, jquery

hudlmo is a collaborative video conferencing web portal with available types of Webinar, Meeting, Huddle and Classes.

Virtual Classroom

Node js, Web sockets, mongodb, javascript, jquery

A web application that provides the experience of a classroom by providing whiteboard facility, live streaming, public chat, private chat with the lecturer, etc.

Leapx

php, zend framework, javascript, jquery, mongodb

Develop an e-Learning system to add courses.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science in University of Colombo School of Computing (3.07 GPA) (2010-2013).

REFEREES

References are available on request.